is dividing the clicks of
cream uh morning and evenings is still
the best
method what do you recommend when
starting out do all the Clicks in the
morning in the evening or half half I
start everybody on once a day in the
morning just to make sure I don't
interfere with their sleep or anything
like that once we get their blood work
back to see how they respond to the
cream then I tell them if they want to
play and do an evening dose they can if
they feel fine doing morning only stick
with with that don't over complicate it
it's 100% trial and error almost and I
think a lot of guys don't like that
those
answers because they just want the
answer but there's not one answer it's
always you got to find what works best
for you and like I said you know I used
to do twice a day on my cream now I do
once a day and I feel fine I I don't
have any issues with that some guys
swear that they need twice a day well
then that's what they need you know like
it really is that simple so you just
gotta you have to be patient try
something stick it out don't just like
try it for a few days and go oh you know
you really have to be patient um to see
how these things are going to play out
so with a cream adjustment like I said
three to four weeks I would say at least
unless you're just horrible I mean if
you change something and like you're
amped up your heart's racing and you
can't sleep and you feel terrible like
you're gonna die okay like don't do your
cream the next day and get it you know
and then drop it back but that's rare um
these these changes are usually pretty
subtle um so really just just play with
it and see what works best for you the
twice a day some guys love it some guys
think it's a hassle so it just depends
yeah
[Music]